[  
An independent travel network](https://www.guestreservations.com/ "Guest Reservations")

[Groups (9+ Rooms)](https://groups.guestreservations.com/Group-Rate/ "Groups (9+ Rooms)") [Travel Guides](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/news "Travel Guides") [My Booking](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/mybooking "My Booking")

Privacy Policy
==============

We value your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the information collected when you visit the website guestreservations.com (the “Site”) and use the Services (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/termsofuse "Terms of Use")) and how Guest Reservations (“Travel Agent,” “Guest Reservations,” “we,” or “us”) uses and discloses that information. When you make a booking through the Site, your information is transferred to the respective hotel where you book. Through the Services, we may also display and send you deals that may be interesting to you. You agree to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy by using the Site and Services. You should immediately cease using the Site and Services if you do not agree.

### Children

Guest Reservations does not seek to collect personal information about children under 13, and you must be 18 or older to use the Site. We may collect information from parents or guardians about family reservations with their consent. If we learn and have actual knowledge of a child providing information through the Site, we will delete such information as soon as possible. We will honor requests by a parent or guardian to review or delete information about their child.

### Security

Guest Reservations values data security and uses reasonable safeguards to protect personal information against loss and theft, including data encryption, restricted access, and firewalls where applicable. However, security over the internet or in any circumstance cannot be guaranteed. Guest Reservations does not assume any responsibility for any harm, loss, or damage you may experience or incur by the sending of personal or confidential information over the internet, and you should take your own measures to protect your sensitive information. If you have any questions about the security of our Site, contact us through our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us").

### Information Collected

We collect and use customer information as necessary to deliver great service to our customers (including telling our customers about our hotel reservation services, deals, and other opportunities through email) and to run and improve our business (which includes our reservation services and marketing). When you use our Site or Services, we may collect the following kinds of personal information from you as needed:

Reservation Information and Customer Support. You can browse the Site without revealing “personal” information. However, to use parts of the Services, such as making a hotel reservation, we require you to provide personal identifiers such as your name, phone number, contact information, and billing information. If you make a booking, we also collect commercial information about your transaction and reservation, and other personal information as indicated on the Site. You may also provide us with information when you communicate with our customer support. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular feature. By providing information to us, you agree that the information is true, accurate, and complete and that you have authorization to provide it to us.

Account Information. When you create or use an account, you provide us with related account information, such as your email address and a password. When you provide your email address and create or use your account, we may offer promotional codes and other discounts or offers, from time to time, to be applied to your booking; and we may send you marketing emails with offers that may be interesting to you. Your use is conditioned upon any terms referenced along with the discount or other offer; and you opt-in to this part of the Services by selecting to sign up for and use your account. You may withdraw from this feature at any time by emailing us through our contact page or following unsubscribe instructions in each email. Any discount or offer is reasonably related to the good-faith estimate of the value of the data and our interest in providing offers to customers based on our experience as an independent travel network helping numerous consumers.

Public Content. We may collect information that you publicly upload, such as when you post a review or comment about Guest Reservations.

Device and Internet Connection Information; Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. The Site uses cookies and similar technologies to store your preferences, display content based upon what you view to personalize your visit, analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements around the Site, serve targeted and personalized advertising and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information collected may include Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), geolocation information, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you, and we may receive reports based on the data from these technologies. Although these activities involve developing an understanding of you as a user, we use this information for the purposes described.

Guest Reservations Cookies (First Party Cookies): We use our cookies to improve your web-browsing experience. Guest Reservations cookies are associated with your Personal Data, however, no third party may use the information we collect through Guest Reservation cookies for their own purposes.

Third Party Cookies: We work with third parties that place cookies on our Site to provide their services, including:

Ad Targeting: We work with third parties that may place and access their own cookies in the course of serving advertisements on this Site. These companies may use information obtained through their cookies (which do not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) to serve relevant ads on our Site. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not ours.

Data Providers: We also allow data providers to collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), when you visit our Site, or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect demographic or other data, with identifying elements removed, linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may disclose with data providers solely in hashed, non-human readable form.

Analytics/Measurement: We also use third-party analytics cookies to gain insight into how our visitors use the Site and optimize and improve our Site. The data we gather includes which web pages you have viewed, which referring/exit pages you have entered and arrived from, which platform type you have used, date and time stamp information, and details such as the number of clicks you make on a given page, your mouse movements and scrolling activity, the search words you use and the text you type while using our Site.

Remarketing Pixel Tags: We may disclose website usage information with third-party advertising companies for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising companies may place or recognize a cookie on your computer or device. We will then use the information that is collected to serve you relevant advertisements when you are visiting other sites on the internet. These advertisements may be targeted to specific searches you conducted on Guest Reservations during earlier browsing sessions.

Notice of Right to Opt-Out of Sale/Sharing: To opt-out of data “selling” or data “sharing” if applicable to you, which may include certain third-party marketing and other types of non-essential cookies, please utilize our simple [opt out form](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/privacy/donotsell) for **Your Privacy Choices** here: [https://www.guestreservations.com/about/privacy/donotsell](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/privacy/donotsell)

You may also use an opt-out preference signal like the Global Privacy Control (“GPC”) to opt out of the “selling” or “sharing” of your personal information through tools such as marketing cookies. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.guestreservations.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you have any questions about third-party privacy practices, please see their respective privacy policies and the links below.

For Google and Doubleclick, click here: [https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en).

For Google Analytics, click here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

For other questions about Google’s privacy practices, you can also click here: [https://business.safety.google/privacy/](https://business.safety.google/privacy/).

For Microsoft/Bing, click here: [https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings](https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings)

For Criteo, click here: [https://www.criteo.com/privacy/](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/).

For Clicktripz, click here: [https://www.clicktripz.com/privacy/opt\_out.php](https://www.clicktripz.com/privacy/opt_out.php)

For Meta/Facebook, click here: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy/](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policy/).

For Mapbox, click here: [https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy](https://www.mapbox.com/legal/privacy).

In addition, to generally (i.e., not just for this Site) opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising visit the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website or click here: [https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). If you are located in the European Union, please click here: [https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

Please keep in mind that without cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Site. Removing all cookies from your computer could also affect your subsequent visits to certain websites, including this Site, by requiring that, for example, you enter your information each time you return to that website.

Mobile Devices: We and/or our data providers may collect and store a unique identifier matched to your mobile device in order to deliver customized ads or content while you use applications or surf the internet, or to identify you in a unique manner across other devices or browsers. In order to customize these ads or content, we or a data partner may collect demographic or other data, with identifying elements removed, about you received from third parties, as well as data you voluntarily have submitted to us (e.g., your email address) and/or data passively collected from you, such as your device identifier or IP address. For advertising purposes, however, we will share your email address with our data partners solely in hashed, non-human readable form. If you no longer wish to receive interest-based advertising on your mobile device browser or applications, please refer to your device's operating system settings, or follow instructions below.

Android Users (version 2.3 and above): To use the "opt-out of interest-based advertising" option, follow the instructions provided by Google here: [https://support.google.com/googleplay/answer/3405269](https://support.google.com/googleplay/answer/3405269)

iOS users (version 6 and above): To use the "Limit Ad-Tracking" option, follow the instructions provided by Apple here: [https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074). You can also use the tools available at [https://youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) and [https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice) to control cookies and similar technologies on your mobile device.

Our Site may also include social media features, such as Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram buttons (“Features”). These Features may collect your IP address and information about page visits and may set a cookie to enable the Features to function properly. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. For more information, see the policies of Facebook/Meta, Instagram, and Twitter.

Third-Party Information. We may get information from third parties, such as transaction information, which includes information about your booking and transaction ID, and customer service information, to help facilitate your booking and provide the Services to you. We may also get information from third parties, including public information, such as verification services and consumer reporting agencies (to comply with regulatory requirements, ensure data accuracy, and prevent fraud, for example). We use this information to develop, offer, and deliver our Services, to process transactions, and to obey legal and regulatory requirements. We do not buy third-party data lists for marketing new content to you. We may also receive certain data, such as device or booking data, from third-party cookies or applications (e.g., Google and Facebook), our affiliates or partners, and individuals purchasing services on your behalf. If you provide data about other individuals to make a purchase, you agree to have consent for the data sharing and that each individual consents to our privacy practices.

Public and Other Information. We may collect and display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements. By posting public content about us, you consent that we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us through our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us"). We may collect information from you related to a promotion, when you communicate with us or with our customer support, or when you otherwise provide it to us. We may also draw inferences about your preferences from the information described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use information about offers you have viewed or purchased to show you more relevant content.

### Retention of Information

We will retain your information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, including to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, enforce our legal agreements, and resolve disputes. We may use partners and service providers to help us retain information, subject to the provisions in this Privacy Policy.

Our retention of personal information considers various factors, such as our relationship with you, and whether there is a pending transaction, booking, or account, business or legal obligations to maintain information, including transaction and customer support data, and other considerations, including our other contracts, maintaining evidence, or litigation holds.

### Use of Information

Reservation Services. Guest Reservations is an independent travel network with over 100,000 hotels. We aggregate deals for users by connecting to these different hotels. When you search for or book a reservation, your information is transferred to companies related to our platform, including the respective hotel(s) where you book, to provide, fulfill, confirm, and update your bookings. In other words, you are using the Site to transfer your information to and to interact with these third parties, and we use your information to facilitate the services you request and fulfill our contractual terms. We do not transfer or disclose your personal information to third parties absent this use or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

To Administer and Improve the Services. We use information, such as your activities on the Site, to measure interest in third-party hotel bookings, communicate with you, such as to inform you via email and text message about viewed or booked reservations (including limited follow-up messages to let you know if you did not complete your transaction), send you special offers from Guest Reservations or affiliates, and notifications or updates, customize your experience, improve content and offerings, and analyze use of and improvements to the Site and Services. Likewise, we may use information to provide customer support services.

Legal Purposes. We may use information to detect and protect us against error and criminal activity and enforce our terms and rights. We also use your information to prevent fraud, create reports for analytics and business reporting, facilitate asset transactions, and otherwise comply with legal obligations. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems.

Security. We use information for security purposes, including to authenticate guests and accounts.

Tracking. We use cookies and automated technologies, as described above, to recognize and track new and previous Site visitors, recognize your preferences and devices, review and analyze trends, analyze aggregate and/or anonymized user behavior, administer the Site, track user movements on the Site, gather demographic information to improve the Services and user experience, and display targeted advertisements on the Site and third-party websites. If you have chosen to receive marketing messages, such as by providing your email address or emailing us, we may use information from our log files, cookies, or pixel tags to help us make those communications more useful to you. These uses help improve the Services and offerings.

Marketing. We use information for the legitimate interest of displaying relevant advertising, and we also use information upon your consent, such as for certain marketing. We reserve the right to send you notices that are required by law or needed to service your account. We may use information, such as data collected from cookies, to display and send relevant advertising. We may also use information you provide, or based on your interactions, to send electronic communications to you. If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications or newsletter, you may opt out of receiving them by following instructions in each communication, by emailing us through our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us"), or by calling Customer Service at (866) 238-4218.

### Disclosure of Your Information

The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed in connection with the Services. We may also disclose aggregate and/or anonymized information that does not identify you. If you do not want us to share your personal information as described below, contact us through our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us") or at the contact information listed below.

Hotels. We disclose your information to the respective hotel(s) or other places of accommodation where you book to provide and fulfill your booking requests.

Platform Vendor. The Site uses the platform of a third-party Vendor (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/termsofuse "Terms of Use")) to provide our reservation services and fulfill your reservations; your contact, billing, reservation, and other information may be disclosed to Vendor and any related partners, parents, subsidiaries, and affiliates, when you make a reservation on the Site. While we collect and verify payment data, we only act as the booking agent. Once payment is made and verified, the booking is confirmed and passed on to Vendor to fulfill the reservation, and your information is collected by the Vendor to assist with your bookings and order confirmation, customer services, and our promotional and transactional communications. When an order is confirmed, Vendor's privacy policy and practices, which we do not control, will govern.

Service Providers and Contractors. We share information with service providers, such as payment processors, customer support, and other travel vendors, as necessary to fulfill your requests and provide the Services. Analytics and customer support providers may use information to help us analyze trends and administer the Site and Services. We may likewise share information with “contractors” that are not service providers but to whom we disclose information for a business purpose, for example providing you with products and services that you have requested or considered. We may also from time-to-time contract with third parties to handle surveys on the Site.

Legal Requests. Guest Reservations cooperates with law enforcement and third parties for law enforcement purposes, to protect intellectual property and other rights, and to help protect you and our other customers. We may disclose information as authorized in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials, to respond to a subpoena, court order, or substantially similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

Successor Entities. If Guest Reservations is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may disclose your information for the purpose of the business transaction.

Advertisers. Information is shared with advertisers, including through cookies and other technologies as discussed above, for commercial purposes. For example, we may disclose information to third-party advertisers for cross-context advertising of services related to our Services that may be of interest to you. We may aggregate and disclose information in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. Certain information, such as your name, email address, and password, are not disclosed to these third parties in a personally identifiable manner without your explicit consent.

Selling or Sharing Information. We do not “sell” information for financial compensation. However, under some privacy laws, when information is disclosed, for example when transferring information through cookies and similar technologies, this can be considered selling or sharing data. Subject to certain restrictions, you can opt out of these practices by using the opt-out link available on our Site or contacting us as outlined below.

Public Content. We may disclose public content, such as reviews or testimonials, to other consumers for commercial advertising purposes. For example, we may post user reviews on our Site.

Consent. We may disclose your personal information with your consent.

Finally, although we use reasonable practices to protect your privacy and security, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private or secure.

### Other Websites

This Site contains links to other websites. Guest Reservations is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or their websites, even if they link from the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this Site. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of information.

### Your Rights

Guest Reservations controls the processing of personal information and data on the Site as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We value your privacy rights and strive to provide flexibility with how your personal information is used and shared. Subject to applicable law, you have certain rights and choices with respect to your personal information. Generally, we adhere to the following privacy rights described below, subject to certain limitations authorized by law:

* The right to know and access: You have the right to know what information we have collected about you, where and how we collected it, whether we sell or share the information we have collected about you, and the third parties we might have disclosed your information to. You also have the right to request access to the information we have collected about you in an easily understandable and accessible format.
* The right to amend: You have the right to correct or update personal information we have about you that is inaccurate or incomplete.
* The right to delete: You have the right to delete personal information that we have collected about you (subject to certain exceptions).
* The right to limit: You have the right to limit how we process certain kinds of data about you, for example, any sensitive data.
* The right to opt-out: You have the right to opt-out of certain data practices. For example, you can unsubscribe from our marketing communications (please note that we may still send non-marketing messages, and that consent to receiving marketing communications is not mandatory to use the Services). You have the right to opt out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information to the extent applicable, in particular by using the Your Privacy Choices form linked above. You can also opt out of the use of automated decision-making technology if applicable, in particular by using the Your Privacy Choices form linked above.
* The right to non-discrimination: We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights.
* State Specific Laws: Several states have enacted privacy laws that may apply to you, including if you are a resident of Delaware ,Texas, Virginia, Connecticut, Colorado, Utah, Iowa, Indiana, Tennessee, Oregon, Montana, Florida, New Jersey, New Hampshire, and California. For example, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) governs certain California-related conduct under which you have the right to, among other things, request the categories and/or specific pieces of personal information collected by us, the categories of sources for that personal information, the purposes for which we use that information, the categories of third parties to whom we disclose the information, and the categories of information that we sell or disclose to third parties, free of charge up to twice per year; and for more information about these practices, please see the categories above. Under California's “Shine the Light” law, California residents may also request certain information regarding disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Further, if you are a California resident under the age of 18, California Business & Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content you have publicly posted. Please note that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of public content.
* International Laws: Depending on where you reside, you may have additional rights. For example, generally, residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) have the right to access information we hold about you and to ask that your information be corrected, updated, or erased, and the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing of your information. Our legal basis for collecting and using your personal data is your consent, performance of a contract, or where the collection and use is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights. You may withdraw your consent to our collection and use of your personal data. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your information used in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
* Other Laws: If certain other privacy laws apply to you that afford you with additional rights, please contact us to make a request.

If you would like to make a privacy request or have any questions, please contact us as described below. If you are making a privacy request, we may ask you to verify your identity and request before taking further action.

### Financial Incentives

We may offer incentives related to the collection, retention, or sharing of information that may be deemed a “financial incentive” or “price or service difference.” If you opt in to such an offering pursuant to the terms described at the time of signup, we may collect information like your name and email address. Any difference in price or rate, such as a discount, will be reasonably related to the value of the data. For more information, see the section on Accounts above. If you want to withdraw from the offering, please contact us as described below.

### DNT

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the preferences or settings page of your web browser.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site or providing other notice to you. By continuing to use the Site or Services, you agree to the effective Privacy Policy. You are responsible for checking this Privacy Policy when you visit the Site to review the current policy. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting a new version or by other notice to you.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact Customer Service through our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us") or by calling (866) 238-4218. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please visit our [contact page](https://www.guestreservations.com/about/contact "Contact Us").

This Privacy Policy was updated November 15, 2024.

  An independent travel network

##### Learn more

##### Get in Touch

×

#### Guest ReservationsTM  
Hotel Non-Affiliation – Proudly Independent Network

We are an independent travel network for over 100,000 hotels worldwide. We are not owned or sponsored by any particular hotel, and the trademarks of all hotels in our network are owned by the respective hotels or licensors. We only use hotel trademarks or information to the extent necessary to assist our customers to book rooms in the travel destination of their choice.

**Guest ReservationsTM** Connects Travelers to Relevant Deals:

We are focused on connecting travelers to the most relevant deals.

As an independent travel network and online travel agent (OTA), we can offer rooms through hotel room suppliers and through global distribution systems where hotels place their inventory for sale.

This allows us, as an independent travel network, to get you the same deals you expect with larger travel agencies.

Copyright 2024 **Guest ReservationsTM**.

**Guest ReservationsTM** is an independent travel network  
offering over 100,000 hotels worldwide.
